{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Garage Door Opener Repair Services","appliedActionRules":{"SDB_SCROLLY_SITE_24719":"SDB_SCROLLY_SITE_24719_ctrl"},"categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","__cache./api/resource/task/40260/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":40260,"taskName":"Garage Door Opener - Repair or Adjust","taskDescription":"Repair or Adjust a Garage Door Opener","xmTaskDescriptor":"Garage Door Opener Repair Services","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":100,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"Garage open   adjustment","textMessagingName":"Repr Garage Open","rolloverLongDesc":"Includes not closing or opening, unprompted opening or closing, opening or closing incompletely, strange noises, etc.","rolloverShortDesc":"Diagnoses problem, replaces \u0026 adjusts as needed.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Repair or Adjust a Garage Door Opener.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Garage Door Opener Repair \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Fix Garage Opener","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":36,"acceptGoal":3,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":5,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Garage Door Opener Repair","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Garage Door Opener - Repair or Adjust","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Garage Door Project","urlName":"Garage-Door-Opener-Repair-or-Adjust","taskConsiderationId":1,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":true,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Garage Door Opener Repair Services - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Costs \u0026 Reviews","searchKeywords":"Garage,open,,,adjustment,automatic,Door,Opener,Adjust,problems","emcCategoryOid":-12036,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":567,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"__cache./api/resource/task/interview/40260/":{"taskOID":40260,"originalTaskOID":40260,"setID":567,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":5046,"questionDisplayText":"Repair Needs","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What needs to be repaired? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":2032,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Door works intermittently","answerDisplayText":"Door works intermittently","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6739,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Wall button doesn't work","answerDisplayText":"Wall button doesn't work","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2712,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Gap at bottom of door","answerDisplayText":"Gap at bottom of door","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3580,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Light doesn't work","answerDisplayText":"Light doesn't work","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":203384,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Reprogram remote controls","answerDisplayText":"Reprogram remote controls","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6800,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Want to add keypad/wall console","answerDisplayText":"Want to add keypad/wall console","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6803,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Want to add remote controls","answerDisplayText":"Want to add remote controls","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2017,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Door jammed part way open","answerDisplayText":"Door jammed part way open","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5151,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Remotes don't work","answerDisplayText":"Remotes don't work","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3576,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Light blinks/not working right","answerDisplayText":"Light blinks/not working right","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2029,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"Door won't open","answerDisplayText":"Door won't open","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2028,"answerDisplaySequence":12,"answerText":"Door won't close","answerDisplayText":"Door won't close","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3408,"answerDisplaySequence":13,"answerText":"Keypad doesn't work","answerDisplayText":"Keypad doesn't work","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":14,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":500000,"questionDisplayText":"Type of Garage Door","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of garage door is this? (Select all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"Type of Garage Door","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5718,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Single car garage door","answerDisplayText":"Single car garage door","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2041,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Double car garage door","answerDisplayText":"Double car garage door","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4992,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"RV garage door","answerDisplayText":"RV garage door","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4465,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Other/custom size","answerDisplayText":"Other/custom size","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":5046,"questionDisplayText":"Repair Needs","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What needs to be repaired? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":2032,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Door works intermittently","answerDisplayText":"Door works intermittently","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6739,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Wall button doesn't work","answerDisplayText":"Wall button doesn't work","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2712,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Gap at bottom of door","answerDisplayText":"Gap at bottom of door","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3580,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Light doesn't work","answerDisplayText":"Light doesn't work","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":203384,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Reprogram remote controls","answerDisplayText":"Reprogram remote controls","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6800,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Want to add keypad/wall console","answerDisplayText":"Want to add keypad/wall console","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6803,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Want to add remote controls","answerDisplayText":"Want to add remote controls","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2017,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Door jammed part way open","answerDisplayText":"Door jammed part way open","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5151,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Remotes don't work","answerDisplayText":"Remotes don't work","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3576,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Light blinks/not working right","answerDisplayText":"Light blinks/not working right","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2029,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"Door won't open","answerDisplayText":"Door won't open","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2028,"answerDisplaySequence":12,"answerText":"Door won't close","answerDisplayText":"Door won't close","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3408,"answerDisplaySequence":13,"answerText":"Keypad doesn't work","answerDisplayText":"Keypad doesn't work","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":14,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":2032,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Door works intermittently","answerDisplayText":"Door works intermittently","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6739,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Wall button doesn't work","answerDisplayText":"Wall button doesn't work","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2712,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Gap at bottom of door","answerDisplayText":"Gap at bottom of door","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3580,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Light doesn't work","answerDisplayText":"Light doesn't work","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":203384,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Reprogram remote controls","answerDisplayText":"Reprogram remote controls","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6800,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Want to add keypad/wall console","answerDisplayText":"Want to add keypad/wall console","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6803,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Want to add remote controls","answerDisplayText":"Want to add remote controls","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2017,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Door jammed part way open","answerDisplayText":"Door jammed part way open","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5151,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Remotes don't work","answerDisplayText":"Remotes don't work","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3576,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Light blinks/not working right","answerDisplayText":"Light blinks/not working right","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2029,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"Door won't open","answerDisplayText":"Door won't open","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2028,"answerDisplaySequence":12,"answerText":"Door won't close","answerDisplayText":"Door won't close","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3408,"answerDisplaySequence":13,"answerText":"Keypad doesn't work","answerDisplayText":"Keypad doesn't work","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":14,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":500000,"questionDisplayText":"Type of Garage Door","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of garage door is this? (Select all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"Type of Garage Door","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5718,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Single car garage door","answerDisplayText":"Single car garage door","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2041,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Double car garage door","answerDisplayText":"Double car garage door","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4992,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"RV garage door","answerDisplayText":"RV garage door","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4465,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Other/custom size","answerDisplayText":"Other/custom size","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5718,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Single car garage door","answerDisplayText":"Single car garage door","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2041,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Double car garage door","answerDisplayText":"Double car garage door","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4992,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"RV garage door","answerDisplayText":"RV garage door","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4465,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Other/custom size","answerDisplayText":"Other/custom size","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true}